

Personal Information

Age: 25

Gender: Male

Contact

Phone:

986497274

Email:

mintesfu11@gmail.com

Address:

Dassenech

Language Skills

English - Intermediate, Wolaytta -Intermediate, Amharic - Advanced, Dassenech - Intermediate

Mintesinot Tesfaye

Junior professional

About

I have studied software engineering at Arba Minch University. I'm passionate software developer focused on website development. I've worked in collaboration with my teammates on various projects during my university study. I'm committed to accomplish projects in a given time of period. I have good communication skills and I'm happy to take risks.

Education

Bachelor

Software Engineering Arba Minch University

GPA: 3.93

Jun 2022 Graduation date

Work experience



Nov 2022 - Present

Website

Administrator

Dassenech Woreda Science and Technology office

Feb 2022 - Jul 2022

5 month

Final year project Arba Minch Institute of Technology

Aug 2021 - Dec 2021

4 month Internship

Addis Media Network

Working as Website developer and also providing computer software and hardware maintenance service.

I have developed a Blockchain based voting system in collaboration with my group members

Developed a vehicle dispatching system using codeigniter framework

Certifications

Jul 2022 Certification was issued Employability and job readiness Dereja academy

Extracurricular Activity



5 Jul 2016 - Sep 2016

Environment

Protection

South Ntions, Nationalities &



People's Regional State Youth & Sport Bureau I have participated in the summer season youth voluntary service and I've got good experience.

Additional Skills

Web Development, Communication, Team work, computer Maintenance, Music, Front-End Development, React JS, UI/UX Design, Graphics Design, Pencil drawing

References

Lecturer, Database and Intelligent systems Chair member Arba Minch University Anteneh Tilahun

Contact detail: Email - anteny.amu@gmail.com